mistralsociety.com 2016-05-06

# Privacy Policy, Mistral Society

Mistral Media, LLC (''Mistral Media'', 'us', ''our'' or ''we''), is committed to protecting the privacy and information of all users of our website, products and services. We recognize the importance of your privacy and take it very seriously. This Privacy Policy describes the collection and use of your information when you use our website, products and services. By using our website, products and services, you confirm that have read, understood and agreed to the provisions of this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service. 

Mistral Media LLC follows generally accepted practices for stewardship of data, including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information collected through our website [www.mistralsociety.com](http://www.mistralsociety.com/) and our service accessible from [login.mistralsociety.com](http://login.mistralsociety.com/) The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our Partner has engaged Mistral Media LLC. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@mistralsociety.com.](mailto:privacy@mistralsociety.com?&subject=Privacy)

## Purpose

This Privacy Policy is designed to provide you with information about how we collect, store and use non-personally identifiable and personally identifiable information obtained through our website. 

## Changes to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If we change how we use your personally identifiable information, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy frequently so you are aware of and understand any changes that we may make. 

## Website Functionality

Mistral Media’s website, [www.mistralsociety.com](http://www.mistralsociety.com/), serves two basic functions. First, it is a portal for information about Mistral Media products and services as well as online advertising generally. Second, it contains password-protected pages where Mistral Media partners (“Partners”) can access partner-only materials. 

## General Privacy Policy Practices

Mistral Media follows generally accepted practices for stewardship of data, including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information collected through our website [www.mistralsociety.com](http://www.mistralsociety.com/) and our service accessible from [login.mistralsociety.com](http://login.mistralsociety.com/) The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which our Partner has engaged Mistral Media. If you have questions or complaints regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us at [privacy@mistralsociety.com.](mailto:privacy@mistralsociety.com?&subject=Privacy)

## **** Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information

Personally identifiable information is any information that may be used to identify or contact you personally, such as your name, email address, gender, birthdate, phone number, postal or other physical address. Because of the nature of the services we provide, we must collect certain personally identifiable information during the registration process if you sign up for our services (e.g. you are a Partner), including your name and email address. You may also provide personal information to us when participating in a survey or poll or when you post information on our website or otherwise contact us. Whether or not to provide this information is your choice; however, certain personally identifiable information is required to access and use some of the services. No personally identifiable information is collected on this website from consumers that browse the website for information.

We do not merge any of the personally identifiable information collected via our contact form with other anonymous data collected on our website.

We collect the following kinds of personal information from our Partners when they sign-up to use our services:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password

We use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order

  * Send you an order confirmation

  * Enable certain features of the services

  * Provide service and support

  * For security and identification purposes

  * To contact you as described in this Privacy Policy

  * Provide, maintain and improve the services

  * Send you requested product or service information

  * Respond to customer service requests

  * Administer your account

  * Send you marketing emails or newsletters

Our Partner's may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [optout@mistralsociety.com](mailto:optout@mistralsociety.com?&subject=OptOut).

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as processing a credit card transaction or offering customer support through a chat feature. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. **  
**

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process

  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,

  * If Mistral Media is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,

  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We may also share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, but this information will not identify you individually.

In order to provide certain services, including self-serve advertising, to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources to verify your address as part of our anti-fraud effort. 

## Non-Personal Information (automatically collected information which doesn’t identify the user):  

We record anonymous data such as traffic logs, number of visits or clicks on a given page, pages viewed or links to our site. We use IP addresses and cookies for gathering website statistics. We also store IP addresses on our server in the event that our site should become corrupted and it becomes necessary to discover the cause of this corruption.

We aggregate this anonymous data as part of managing, maintaining and reporting on use of our website. We may share this anonymous data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with applicable law. We do not rent, sell or share any anonymous data collected on this website with third parties for marketing purposes.

None of this anonymous data is linked to personally identifiable information and we make no attempt to link IP addresses to the individuals who visit this site.

## Cookies  

We use cookies on this website. Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information in entirety upon each visit to a given website.

We serve a cookie from our website when Partners log in to Partner-only pages, so that they can navigate those pages on the site. A randomly-generated anonymous identifier is assigned to this Privacy Policy.

No personally identifiable information is collected by or linked to any of the cookies delivered on our site.

You have the ability to manage the use of cookies on your computer using controls in your web-browser. To learn more about how to manage [cookies click here.](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie)[](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie)   

## Third Party Cookies

The use of cookies by our service providers is covered by our Privacy Policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies to ensure that our site is functioning properly.

## Other Third Party Tracking:

Our third party Partners employ scripts and images that help them better manage content on our site. We do not tie the information gathered to our customers' or users' personally identifiable information.

## Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients:

Mistral Media collects information under the direction of its Partners. Mistral Media has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. Mistral Media works with its Partners to help them provide notice to their customers concerning the purpose for which personal information is collected. 

We collect information for our Partners.  If you are a customer of one of our Partners and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Partners that use our service, please contact the client (i.e. our Partner) that you interact with directly.

Mistral Media has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Mistral Media Partner (the data controller). If the Partner requests Mistral Media to remove the data, Mistral Media will respond to the Partner's request within 30 business days. 

Mistral Media will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Partners for as long as needed to provide services to our Partners. Mistral Media will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Security

The security of your personal information and our clients' information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as login credentials) we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact [privacy@mistralsociety.com.](mailto:privacy@mistralsociety.com?&subject=Privacy)

## Third Party Links

Our website may contain links to other websites.  Because this Privacy Policy only applies to our services and website and not to linked websites, you should examine the privacy policies of any other websites that you access from or through our website. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites.

## Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [privacy@mistralsociety.com.](mailto:privacy@mistralsociety.com?&subject=Privacy) We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

## Children

In order to use our services you must be at least 13 years of age. Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use our services, so this Privacy Policy makes no provision for their use. In the event that a user identifies himself or herself as a child under the age of 13, we will not collect, store or use any personal information of such user. Further, in the event that we receive personal information that we conclude was provided by a child under the age of 13, we will promptly delete such personal information.

## Network Privacy Policy

Mistral Media's network targets ads to consumers who visit our publisher's websites. Mistral Media does not track or maintain personally identifiable information (“PII”) about consumers. We may obtain anonymous information like behavior of a particular user, for example, visiting a particular website, clicking on a particular ad, geographic data and browser type, etc. by using cookies, pixels and IP addresses. 

  * A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows Mistral Media to identify your IP address. Mistral Media may use cookies to track individual responses or views of advertisements.

  * Pixels can be placed on advertisers' pages in order to track when a sale is completed. This helps Mistral Media target future ad placements, but no PII is obtained.

  * Mistral Media may use your IP address to better target ads. Unless you use a static IP address, an IP address relates to households or larger communities. Mistral Media uses IP addresses to track where clicks are coming from and helps us fight click fraud, but no PII is obtained.

  * Information can be collected directly from Mistral Media advertisements or indirectly through Publishers that Mistral Media works with.

  * Mistral Media may set a cookie on your computer or associate behavior with your Internet service provider's IP address when you click on an advertisement delivered on publisher websites. After a behavior is associated to a cookie or an IP address, Mistral Media may track how you interact with the advertisement and the publisher website.

## Use of Information and Data

Mistral Media may share anonymous information about your behaviors with trusted publishers under confidentiality agreements. These publishers may use this information to better target advertisements to you. 

Mistral Media stores anonymous information in a database. This database is password protected and secure. Mistral Media maintains the data in an encrypted form, so that even if the data is improperly accessed, it is less likely to be in an intelligible format. The data is encrypted and password protected and only accessed to resolve a legal or business issue. Mistral Media cannot guarantee that its security or privacy protection measures will prevent its computers from being illegally accessed and the data stolen. 

## Privacy Practices of Third Parties

Publishers who place advertisements on the internet may use their own cookies, web beacons and other technology to collect information about you. Mistral Media does not control publishers' use of such technology and shall have no responsibility or liability for such use.

To learn about how a particular publisher may use your PII or anonymous information, you should read the privacy policy of that publisher.   

## Questions?

Please contact us at Mistral Media, 2699 Pacific Coast Highway, Suite 101, Hermosa Beach, CA 90254 with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.

Effective Date: August 28, 2015
